adminschoice.com 2006-06-16

# Privacy Statement

| 

[**Performance Monitoring -   iostat , vmstat & netstat **](http://www.adminschoice.com/docs/iostat_vmstat_netstat.htm)\- Introduction to performance monitoring tools with example and command  syntax.
[**Veritas Volume Manager-1**](http://www.adminschoice.com/docs/vxvm.htm) : 
Using vxdiskadm to add &  manage disks & disk groups .
[**Veritas Volume Manager-2**](http://www.adminschoice.com/docs/vxassist.htm) : 
Using vxassist to create ,configure &  manage volumes .
[**Admin's Guide to Solstice Disk Suite**](http://www.adminschoice.com/docs/solstice_disksuite.htm) : Complete practical reference including root mirroring and trouble shooting.
[**Securing Solaris**](http://www.adminschoice.com/docs/securing_solaris.htm) : 
A few suggestions to make your Solaris system secure from internal and external intrusion.
 
Step by step guide to Solaris Installation.
Network  installation of Solaris over one or multiple systems. 
Details of Solaris  booting process. 
Common booting related error messages and their possible solution
Setting up DNS server
[**Trouble Shooting DNS  **](http://www.adminschoice.com/docs/dns_trouble_shooting.htm) Some of the configuration and nslookup related errors explained.
Server , Clients setup and commands. 
Reference table of important parameters and their values.
Alphabetical listing of common Solaris Error Messages and their explanation
[**Checking & Repairing File systems with fsck** ](http://www.adminschoice.com/docs/fsck.htm)  fsck operation ,syntax and explanation of some common error messages
vi basics for  reference
explanations.
 
**Open Directory**    
**Sun.com    **

**FAQs**
**:**
**Unix**
:
**Solaris Documentation**
:
**Sun**
:
**Documentation Home**
:
**Patches & Softwares**
:
**Certification Info  **
|   
---|---  
  
| 

The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [ adminschoice.com ](http://www.adminschoice.com/)

** Personal Information**
This Web site does not request any personal information except when you want to contact site administrator /webmaster and that information is used only for reply if needed . 
We do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any other unspecified purpose .
     
** External Links**
This site contains links to other sites. adminschoice.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
     
** Public Forums**
This site has  discussion forums available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
     
**Advertisers**
We do not use cookies on this site .However there may be cookies associated with some of the advertisement on our website  which are controlled directly by advertising company  & we do not have access to this information.
     
**Contacting the Web Site**
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
